Benjamin B. French Family Papers
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- Part II: Oversize, 1819-1893 (Box II:OV 1-6)
  - Miscellany (Box II:OV 2)
    - Certificates and awards
      - French, Benjamin B., 1819-1870 (Container II:21)
    - Child's cut-out toys, 1840s (Container II:21) (Box II:OV 3)
    - Scrapbooks, French, Francis O. (Box II:OV 4)
      - Vol. 1, 1843-1893 (Container II:22)
    - Broadside, reward for capture of President Lincoln's assassins, 1865, April 20 (Container II:OV 4) (Box II:OV 5)
    - Speeches and writings (Box II:OV 6)
      - French, Benjamin B., draft of memoir, 1856 (Container II:24)